Paul Muldoon papers, 1939-2010
Emory University
- Writings by Muldoon, circa 1960s-2004, Series 2; Boxes 8-30, 66-84 and OP 2-9, 163-167
  - Poetry, circa 1960s-2003, Subseries 2.1; Boxes 8-23, 66-73 and OP 2-4, 163, 165
    - "November," single corrected typescript (Box 13, Folder 18)
    - "The O-O's Party" [See Subseries 2.4, Children's Poetry] (Box -, Folder -)
    - "The Patrons," multiple typescript drafts with holograph notes (Box 13, Folder 19)
    - "The Pen-Pal," single holograph draft (Box 13, Folder 20)
    - "The Perimeter Fence," single typescript (Box 13, Folder 21)
    - "Pillow Talk," single typescript (Box 13, Folder 22)
    - "Promises, Promises," single typescript [See also Mules and "Going Away"] (Box 13, Folder 23)
    - "Rapunzel," single corrected typescript (Box 13, Folder 24)
    - "Sir Walter," single typescript (Box 13, Folder 25)
    - "Small Talk," single typescript draft [See also "The Love Poem" and "Her Last Man"] (Box 13, Folder 26)
    - "Stampede" [variant title for "The Widow-Maker"], single corrected typescript (Box 13, Folder 27)
    - "Sweet Nothings," single corrected typescript (Box 13, Folder 28)
    - "The Swing," single typescript (Box 13, Folder 29)
    - "A Stray Bullet," single typescript (Box 13, Folder 30)
    - "The Studio," single typescript (Box 13, Folder 31)
    - The Unicorn Defends Himself, title page with third stanza and postcard of painting from the Metropolitan Museum of Art (Box 13, Folder 32)
    - "When I was in Holy Angels Grade School.. ." holograph draft (Box 13, Folder 33)
    - "When Ulysses braved the wine-dark sea.. ." holograph draft (Box 13, Folder 34)
    - "The world on a plate.. ." single corrected typescript (Box 13, Folder 35)
    - "Yggdrasill," multiple typescript drafts (Box 13, Folder 36)
    - "The Young Executive," single typescript (Box 13, Folder 37)
    - Untitled fragments and loose notes (Box 13, Folder 38)
    - Untitled fragments and loose notes (circa 1980-83) (Box 13, Folder 39)
    - Typescript and holograph lists of poems for readings (Box 13, Folder 40)
    - "The Winnebago Trickster Cycle," photocopy of source material for "The More a Man Has.. ." (Box 13, Folder 41)
    - Meeting the British (1987)
    - "Christo," multiple typescript drafts (Box 13, Folder 42)
    - "The Fox," single corrected typescript (Box 13, Folder 43)
    - "Poplars," multiple typescript drafts (Box 13, Folder 44)
    - "Profumo," multiple typescript drafts (Box 13, Folder 45)
    - "7, Middagh Street: Wystan," multiple typescript drafts with holograph notes (Box 13, Folder 46)
    - "7, Middagh Street: Gypsy," multiple typescript drafts (Box 13, Folder 47)
    - "7, Middagh Street: Ben," multiple typescript drafts with holograph notes (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - "7, Middagh Street: Chester" [See "Other Women"] (Box -, Folder -)
    - "7, Middagh Street: Salvador,"multiple typescript drafts (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - "7, Middagh Street: Carson," multiple typescript drafts with holograph notes (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - "7, Middagh Street: Louis," multiple typescript drafts with holograph notes (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - "7, Middagh Street," sources and secondary materials (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - Miscellaneous notes and fragments, including some fragments of poems from Meeting the British (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - "The Toe-Tag," single corrected typescript (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - Untitled fragment toward "7, Middagh Street," corrected typescript [begins "A windswept gallery.. ."] (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - Meeting the British, photocopied cover art for Wake Forest edition (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - Meeting the British, corrected typescripts of Table of Contents and Acknowledgements (Box 14, Folder 10)
    - Meeting the British, complete typescript with holograph corrections and notes re: publication of individual poems (Box 14, Folder 11)
    - Meeting the British, photocopies of page proofs for Faber and Faber edition (Box 14, Folder 12)
    - Miscellaneous Poems, circa 1983-1986
    - "Anthrax," multiple typescript drafts (Box 14, Folder 13)
    - "As for the Quince" [translation from Nuala Ní Dhomhnaill], single typescript (Box 14, Folder 14)
    - "The Barn Dance," single corrected typescript (Box 14, Folder 15)
    - "Bears," single typescript (Box 14, Folder 16)
    - "Bloom Sunday," single typescript [See also Mules] (Box 14, Folder 17)
    - "Blow by Blow," single typescript with "Ducan!" written at top (Box 14, Folder 18)
    - "The Brownlows," single typescript (Box 14, Folder 19)
    - "Caprice des Dieux," single typescript (Box 14, Folder 20)
    - "Cuckoo Comes," single typescript with holograph note re: title (Box 14, Folder 21)
    - "The Drowned Blackbird" translated from Seamus Dall Mac Cuarta, with letter from Robert Johnstone, 9 October 1984 [See also Subseries 2.3, Translations] (Box 14, Folder 22)
    - "Emily," multiple typescript drafts (Box 14, Folder 23)
    - "Excitable Boy," single typescript (Box 14, Folder 24)
    - "Failure," single typescript with holograph note (Box 14, Folder 25)
    - "Fugue," single typescript (Box 14, Folder 26)
    - "Gold," multiple typescript drafts (Box 14, Folder 27)
    - "The Hoodlum Priest," single typescript with minimal correction (Box 14, Folder 28)
    - "Literally," single corrected typescript (Box 14, Folder 29)
    - "Living at This Hour," typescript and holograph drafts with title page (Box 14, Folder 30)
    - "Liz," single typescript (Box 14, Folder 31)
    - "The Main Mast," single typescript (Box 14, Folder 32)
    - "Other Women," multiple typescript drafts (Box 14, Folder 33)
    - "The Ox," single typescript with holograph note (Box 14, Folder 34)
    - "Pandas," single typescript (Box 14, Folder 35)
    - "Paul Klee: They're Biting," photocopy of poem with note re: line break (Box 14, Folder 36)
    - "Precautions" [translated from Martin Sorescu], single typescript [See also Subseries 2.3, Translations] (Box 14, Folder 37)
    - "The Raisin," single typescript (Box 14, Folder 38)
    - "The Right Arm," single corrected typescript (Box 14, Folder 39)
    - "Snogging," holograph draft with typescript title page (Box 14, Folder 40)
    - "Sylvia," single typescript (Box 14, Folder 41)
    - "Tibet," single typescript (Box 14, Folder 42)
    - "Tiffin with Borges," single typescript (Box 14, Folder 43)
    - "Toxophilus," single corrected typescript (Box 14, Folder 44)
    - "Under Saturn," single typescript (Box 14, Folder 45)
    - "Wolves," multiple typescript drafts (Box 14, Folder 46)
    - "The Yard," single corrected typescript with letter from Alan Jenkins, Times Literary Supplement (Box 14, Folder 47)
    - "Yellow Ragwort," single typescript (Box 14, Folder 48)
    - Manuscript and typescript fragments (Box 14, Folder 49)
    - Notes on napkins (Box 14, Folder 50)
    - Multiple holograph notes re: reading sets (Box 14, Folder 51)
    - Selected Poems 1968-1983 (1986)
    - Selected Poems, 1968-1986; camera copy for 1993 Farrar, Straus, and Giroux edition of Ecco edition, with TLS from Paul Elie, 6 December 1993 (Box 14, Folder 52)
    - Madoc: A Mystery (1990)
    - Acknowledgements, multiple typescript drafts (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - "Abelard," multiple typescript drafts with holograph notes (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - "Adorno," multiple typescript drafts with holograph notes (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - "Aenesidemus," multiple typescript drafts (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - "Anaxagoras," multiple typescript drafts (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - "Anaximander," uncorrected typescript (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - "Anselm," single typescript with holograph corrections (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - "Antisthenes," typescript with holograph notes (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - "Aquinas," single corrected typescript (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - "Arendt," multiple typescript drafts with holograph notes (Box 15, Folder 10)
    - "Arnauld," multiple typescript drafts (Box 15, Folder 11)
    - "Ascham," multiple typescript drafts (Box 15, Folder 12)
    - "Asra," single uncorrected typescript (Box 15, Folder 13)
    - "Austin," multiple typescript drafts with holograph notes (Box 15, Folder 14)
    - "Ayer," holograph notes (Box 15, Folder 15)
    - "Bachelard," multiple typescript drafts with holograph notes (Box 15, Folder 16)
    - "Bacon," multiple typescript drafts (Box 15, Folder 17)
    - "Baird," multiple typescript drafts (Box 15, Folder 18)
    - "Bakhtin," multiple typescript drafts (Box 15, Folder 19)
    - "Barnet," multiple typescript drafts (Box 15, Folder 20)
    - "Barthes," multiple typescript drafts with holograph notes (Box 15, Folder 21)
    - "Bayle," multiple typescript drafts with holograph notes (Box 15, Folder 22)
    - "Bell," multiple typescript drafts with holograph notes (Box 15, Folder 23)
    - "Benedict," multiple typescript drafts with holograph notes (Box 15, Folder 24)
    - "Benjamin," multiple typescript drafts with holograph notes (Box 15, Folder 25)
    - "Bentham," multiple typescript drafts with holograph notes (Box 15, Folder 26)
    - "Bergson," multiple typescript drafts with holograph notes (Box 15, Folder 27)
    - "Boehme," multiple typescript drafts with holograph notes (Box 15, Folder 28)
    - "Boethius," multiple typescript drafts (Box 15, Folder 29)
    - "Bohr," multiple typescript drafts with holograph notes (Box 15, Folder 30)
    - "Boole," multiple typescript drafts with holograph notes (Box 15, Folder 31)
    - "Boyle," corrected typescript (Box 15, Folder 32)
    - "Bradley," holograph notes (Box 15, Folder 33)
    - "Brahe," holograph notes (Box 15, Folder 34)
    - "Brant," multiple typescript drafts with holograph notes (Box 15, Folder 35)
    - "The Briefcase" [variant title "My Holdall,"multiple typescript drafts (Box 15, Folder 36)
    - "Brentano," holograph notes (Box 15, Folder 37)
    - "Bruno," multiple typescript drafts with holograph notes (Box 15, Folder 38)
    - "Buridan," multiple typescript drafts (Box 15, Folder 39)
    - "Burke," multiple typescript drafts with holograph notes (Box 15, Folder 40)
    - "Burnet," multiple typescript drafts with holograph notes (Box 15, Folder 41)
    - "Butler," multiple typescript drafts (Box 15, Folder 42)
    - "Byron," uncorrected typescript (Box 15, Folder 43)
    - "Calvin," corrected typescript with holograph notes (Box 15, Folder 44)
    - "Campanella," corrected typescript (Box 15, Folder 45)
    - "Camus," multiple typescript drafts with holograph notes (Box 15, Folder 46)
    - "Cantor," multiple typescript drafts with holograph notes (Box 15, Folder 47)
    - "Capercailles," multiple typescript drafts (Box 15, Folder 48)
    - "Carnap," multiple typescript drafts with holograph notes (Box 15, Folder 49)
    - "Cauliflowers," single typescript with holograph corrections (Box 15, Folder 50)
    - "Chomsky," multiple typescript drafts with holograph notes (Box 15, Folder 51)
    - "Clarke," multiple typescript drafts with holograph notes (Box 15, Folder 52)
    - "Coleridge," multiple typescript drafts (Box 15, Folder 53)
    - "Collingwood," multiple typescript drafts with holograph notes (Box 15, Folder 54)
    - "Comte," multiple typescript drafts and holograph notes [See also "Newman"] (Box 15, Folder 55)
    - "Cooper," typescript with holograph notes (Box 15, Folder 56)
    - "Copernicus," multiple typescript drafts with holograph notes (Box 15, Folder 57)
    - "Croce," multiple typescript drafts (Box 15, Folder 58)
    - "Darwin," multiple typescript drafts and holograph notes (Box 15, Folder 59)
    - "Dee," single corrected typescript (Box 15, Folder 60)
    - "Democritus," corrected typescript (Box 15, Folder 61)
    - "Derrida," multiple typescript drafts with holograph notes (Box 15, Folder 62)
    - "Descartes," multiple typescript drafts with holograph notes (Box 15, Folder 63)
    - "Dewey," multiple typescript drafts (Box 15, Folder 64)
    - "Dionysius," multiple typescript drafts (Box 15, Folder 65)
    - "Duns Scotus," single corrected typescript (Box 15, Folder 66)
    - "Edison," multiple typescript drafts with holograph notes (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - "Einstein," multiple typescript drafts with holograph notes (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - "Emerson," holograph notes (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - "Epictetus," corrected typescript and holograph note (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - "Erasmus," corrected typescript with holograph notes (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - "Euclid," corrected typescript (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - "Feuerbach," multiple typescript drafts (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - "Fibonacci," uncorrected typescript (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - "Fichte," multiple typescript drafts (Box 16, Folder 9)
    - "Foucault," multiple typescript drafts with holograph notes (Box 16, Folder 10)
    - "Franklin," multiple typescript drafts with holograph notes (Box 16, Folder 11)
    - "Frederick the Great," multiple typescript drafts with holograph notes (Box 16, Folder 12)
    - "Frege," typescript draft with holograph notes (Box 16, Folder 13)
    - "Gadamer," single typescript draft with holograph notes (Box 16, Folder 14)
    - "Galen," multiple typescript drafts with holograph notes (Box 16, Folder 15)
    - "Gass," multiple typescript drafts with holograph notes (Box 16, Folder 16)
    - "Gauss," multiple typescript drafts with holograph notes (Box 16, Folder 17)
    - "Godwin," multiple typescript drafts with holograph notes (Box 16, Folder 18)
    - "Goodman," single uncorrected typescript (Box 16, Folder 19)
    - "Gramsci," multiple typescript drafts with holograph notes (Box 16, Folder 20)
    - "Habermas," multiple typescript drafts (Box 16, Folder 21)
    - "Hakluyt," multiple typescript drafts (Box 16, Folder 22)
    - "Hamilton," multiple typescript drafts with holograph notes (Box 16, Folder 23)
    - "Harman," multiple typescript drafts (Box 16, Folder 24)
    - "Hartley," single corrected typescript (Box 16, Folder 25)
    - "Hartmann," multiple typescript draft with holograph notes (Box 16, Folder 26)
    - "Harvey," multiple typescript drafts (Box 16, Folder 27)
    - "Hawking," multiple typescript drafts with holograph notes (Box 16, Folder 28)
    - "Hegel" [variant title "Rousseau"], multiple typescript drafts (Box 16, Folder 29)
    - "Heidegger," multiple typescript drafts with holograph notes (Box 16, Folder 30)
    - "Heraclitus," multiple typescript drafts (Box 16, Folder 31)
    - "Herbart," multiple typescript drafts with holograph notes (Box 16, Folder 32)
    - "Herrigel," holograph notes (Box 16, Folder 33)
    - "Hobbes," multiple typescript drafts (Box 16, Folder 34)
    - "Hook," multiple typescript drafts with holograph notes (Box 16, Folder 35)
    - "Hooke," typescript draft with holograph notes (Box 16, Folder 36)
    - "Hume," multiple typescript drafts (Box 16, Folder 37)
    - "Husserl," typescript draft (Box 16, Folder 38)
    - "Huxley," multiple typescript drafts and holograph notes (Box 16, Folder 39)
    - "James," single corrected typescript with holograph notes (Box 16, Folder 40)
    - "Jung," multiple typescript drafts with holograph notes (Box 16, Folder 41)
    - "Kant," typescript draft with holograph notes (Box 16, Folder 42)
    - "Kelvin," multiple typescript drafts with holograph notes (Box 16, Folder 43)
    - "Kepler," multiple typescript drafts with holograph notes (Box 16, Folder 44)
    - "Keynes," multiple typescript drafts with holograph notes (Box 16, Folder 45)
    - "Kierkegaard," multiple typescript drafts with holograph notes (Box 16, Folder 46)
    - "Kristeva," single uncorrected typescript (Box 16, Folder 47)
    - "Lacan," multiple typescript drafts with holograph notes (Box 16, Folder 48)
    - "Leibniz," multiple typescript drafts (Box 16, Folder 49)
    - "Levi-Strauss," multiple typescript drafts with holograph notes (Box 16, Folder 50)
    - "Lewis," multiple typescript drafts with holograph notes (Box 16, Folder 51)
    - "Locke," multiple typescript drafts (Box 16, Folder 52)
    - "Lovejoy," multiple typescript drafts (Box 16, Folder 53)
    - "Luther," multiple typescript drafts (Box 16, Folder 54)
    - "Mach," multiple typescript drafts with holograph notes (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - "Machiavelli," corrected typescript (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - "Maimon," multiple typescript drafts (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - "Maimonedes," corrected typescript (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - "Malebranche," multiple typescript drafts (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - "Malthus," multiple typescript drafts (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - "Mandeville," multiple typescript drafts with holograph notes (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - "Marconi," uncorrected typescript with holograph notes (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - "Marcuse," holograph notes (Box 17, Folder 9)
    - "Marx," multiple typescript drafts with holograph notes (Box 17, Folder 10)
    - "Maxwell," multiple typescript drafts with holograph notes (Box 17, Folder 11)
    - "McTaggart," typescript draft with holograph notes (Box 17, Folder 12)
    - "Meinong," multiple typescript drafts (Box 17, Folder 13)
    - "Merleau-Ponty," multiple typescript drafts with holograph notes (Box 17, Folder 14)
    - "Mill," multiple typescript drafts with holograph notes (Box 17, Folder 15)
    - "Moore," multiple typescript drafts (Box 17, Folder 16)
    - "More," multiple typescript drafts (Box 17, Folder 17)
    - "Neurath," multiple typescript drafts with holograph notes (Box 17, Folder 18)
    - "Newman," multiple typescript drafts, including fragment from "Comte" (Box 17, Folder 19)
    - "Newton," multiple typescript drafts (Box 7, Folder 20)
    - "Nietzsche," multiple typescript drafts (Box 17, Folder 21)
    - "Nozick," typescript draft with holograph notes (Box 17, Folder 22)
    - "Occam," multiple typescript drafts with holograph notes (Box 17, Folder 23)
    - "Origen," multiple typescript drafts with holograph notes (Box 17, Folder 24)
    - "Ortega," multiple typescript drafts with holograph notes (Box 17, Folder 25)
    - "Paine," uncorrected typescript (Box 17, Folder 26)
    - "The Panther," multiple typescript drafts (Box 17, Folder 27)
    - "Paracelsus," holograph notes (Box 17, Folder 28)
    - "Pascal," multiple typescript drafts with holograph notes (Box 17, Folder 29)
    - "Pasteur," multiple typescript drafts with holograph notes (Box 17, Folder 30)
    - "Peirce," multiple typescript drafts with holograph notes (Box 17, Folder 31)
    - "Plotinus," corrected typescript (Box 17, Folder 32)
    - "Popper," multiple typescript drafts with holograph notes (Box 17, Folder 33)
    - "Priestley," multiple typescript drafts (Box 17, Folder 34)
    - "Proclus," multiple typescript drafts with holograph notes (Box 17, Folder 35)
    - "Protagoras," multiple typescript drafts (Box 17, Folder 36)
    - "Pseudo-Dionysius," multiple typescript drafts (Box 17, Folder 37)
    - "Putnam," multiple typescript drafts with holograph notes (Box 17, Folder 38)
    - "Pyrrho," multiple typescript drafts and holograph notes (Box 17, Folder 39)
    - "Pythagoras," typescript draft (Box 17, Folder 40)
    - "Quine," typescript draft with holograph notes (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - "Reid," multiple typescript drafts with holograph notes (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - "Ricoeur," uncorrected typescript with holograph notes (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - "Royce," multiple typescript drafts with holograph notes (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - "Russell," multiple typescript drafts (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - "Rutherford," multiple typescript drafts (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - "Ryle," multiple typescript drafts with holograph notes (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - "Santayana," single uncorrected typescript (Box 18, Folder 8)
    - "Sartre," multiple typescript drafts with holograph notes (Box 18, Folder 9)
    - "Saussure," multiple typescript drafts with holograph notes (Box 18, Folder 10)
    - "Scaliger," multiple typescript drafts with holograph notes (Box 18, Folder 11)
    - "Schiller," multiple typescript drafts (Box 18, Folder 12)
    - "Schlick," multiple typescript drafts with holograph notes (Box 18, Folder 13)
    - "Schopenhauer," multiple typescript drafts with holo notes (Box 18, Folder 14)
    - "Seneca," multiple typescript drafts (Box 18, Folder 15)
    - "Smith," typescript draft with holograph notes (Box 18, Folder 16)
    - "Socrates," corrected typescript (Box 18, Folder 17)
    - "Sorel," multiple typescript drafts (Box 18, Folder 18)
    - "Southey," multiple typescript drafts (Box 18, Folder 19)
    - "Spencer," multiple typescript drafts with holograph notes (Box 18, Folder 20)
    - "Spinoza," single corrected typescript with holograph notes (Box 18, Folder 21)
    - "Strawson," multiple typescript drafts with holograph notes (Box 18, Folder 22)
    - "Tarski," multiple typescript drafts with holograph notes (Box 18, Folder 23)
    - "Tea," multiple corrected typescripts with holograph notes (Box 18, Folder 24)
    - "Thales," single corrected typescript (Box 18, Folder 25)
    - "Thoreau," holograph notes (Box 18, Folder 26)
    - "Toland," multiple typescript drafts with holograph notes (Box 18, Folder 27)
    - "Unamuno," multiple typescript drafts (Box 18, Folder 28)
    - "Voltaire," multiple typescript drafts (Box 18, Folder 29)
    - "Watt," multiple typescript drafts with holograph notes (Box 18, Folder 30)
    - "Whitehead," multiple typescript drafts (Box 18, Folder 31)
    - "Wittgenstein," typescript draft with holograph notes (Box 18, Folder 32)
    - "Wollstonecraft," typescript draft (Box 18, Folder 33)
    - "Wycliffe," corrected typescript (Box 18, Folder 34)
    - "Zeno," corrected typescript (Box 18, Folder 35)
    - Madoc, partial typescript Title Page through "Leibniz," circa 34 pages (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - Madoc, partial early manuscript (all holograph notes) "Butler" to Hawking," circa 51 pages (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - Madoc, partial typescript "Thales" to "Huxley," circa 80 pages (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - Madoc, partial typescript "Thales" to "Bohr," circa 83 pages (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - Madoc, partial typescript circa 105 pages (original grouping preserved) (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - Madoc, partial typescript circa 109 pages (original grouping preserved) (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - Madoc, partial manuscript, holograph and typescript drafts circa 198 pages (original grouping preserved) (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - Madoc, unidentified typescript and holograph drafts (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - Madoc, unidentified typescript and holograph drafts (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - Madoc, unidentified holograph notes (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - Madoc, unidentified holograph notes, found between "Cauliflowers" and "Adorno" typescripts (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - Madoc, unidentified holograph notes, original grouping preserved (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - Madoc, unidentified holograph notes with several typescript drafts (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - Madoc, early title and contents pages with two typescript drafts of "Acknowledgements" (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - Madoc, rough holograph outlines (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - Madoc, holograph progress report/checklist (July 20, 1989 and August 28, 1989) (Box 20, Folder 9)
    - Madoc, research photocopies (Box 20, Folder 10)
    - Madoc, late manuscript draft with pages left blank, circa 158 pages (Box 20, Folder 11)
    - Madoc, final manuscript (Box 20, Folder 12)
    - Madoc, page proofs [See also Miscellaneous Poems, circa 1986-1996] (Box 20, Folder 13)
    - Madoc book covers (Box OP2)
    - Incantata (1994)
    - "Incantata," single corrected typescript page (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - "Incantata," corrected typescript (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - "Incantata," page proofs with cover letter and envelope from Graphic Studio Dublin (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - Art/ promotional posters for "Incantata": 3 posters of "Incantata" painting, four posters of painting with announcement/ brief profile of Mary Farl Powers as ArtsLink Artist of the Month, October 1995 [See also Annals of Chile for Mary Farl Powers painting] (Box OP3)
    - The Prince of the Quotidian (1994)